So what about,
so what about, so thoughts, slab culture
that
you're thinking of,
Ben? I've been thinking it's hard to come to
a robust conclusion,
but...
I think...
Yeah,
what does that even mean, that's really?
I think it's important to understand that we
are,
we're making us something.
Self -driving lab,
and so AI will be in heavy use,
and AI should be running
tests and gathering data
and analyzing data,
but I think it's important to emphasize the fact
that we should be understanding data,
and we should be understanding even, even
like,
before we even, like,
start, I don't even know if before we start using
AI, because,
no, not that.
But we should understand what everyone is doing,
at least at a
base level. Like,
of course, like, I think
if we are able to do that ourselves, that's,
like, ideal, I don't know if that's necessary
for everything. Yeah,
that happens in this last.
Like, it's being strategic about what you choose
to really dig into and what you choose to just
kind of let go and say. Yeah,
I can handle this. Yeah.
Or what you choose to say.
I'm going to
ask the expert, you know, somebody that you trust,
if it's about trust,
but you don't, like, that's not your goal to,
like, learn this thing really in depth, then,
yeah, maybe you bring that somebody else.
And I think a big thing that a
lot of people in this lab are talking about,
and I think is a really great point, is when
it comes to writing papers and preparing for
presentations, doing things like that,
where it is AI player role.
that and how, what's a culture around that?
I think that's been the main topic of
interest for most people that have been bringing
this up. Yeah, I'm just not there yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, and I think I've, I've had a certain rush
that I felt with the summer,
with getting some early papers out,
with graduation timelines for some people that
are going to be applying to grad school and
having a publication,
is a very big deal for grad school.
Like, it's not like you can't get into grad school
without publications, but it can really set you
apart.
So that, like, some of these timelines are on
my mind, and I think I felt a certain rush.
Like, okay, like, let's get these papers out.
Let's write some grants based on those,
you know. So I think that it would also be too
easy for me to just stay in that mindset.
And they're like, well, that's just,
let's just keep doing that.
And so I think that there are a couple things
that come to mind. One would be
having more practice presentations with the whole
group where
questions,
like a really big focus on the Q &A.
So, like, ask questions, and we're not trying
to grill the person,
but, but,
and make sure it's clear.
Like, it is okay to just, like,
I don't know. Yeah.
That was something that I didn't have strong
oversight into, like, I'll go back.
So it was almost like the purpose of the practice
session. could be to help identify key points.
What you don't know. Yeah, like what you don't
know, what you don't understand fully.
Which I'm sure will be awkward and difficult
to just be like, yeah, let me put myself out
there.
But I wonder if that's...
Do you have any specifics of, like,
things we could do that?
I think that would be really helpful if we were
to do that. I think,
I
wonder if there could be some form of,
like,
AI could write the first draft of a
paper that then we read
and really understand. And if there are things
that we don't understand,
either have a tell AI, like, we don't need
to talk about that, or really dig deep.
Yeah. Because I think AI could give us a map
and help us in that process of figuring out what
we don't really understand and what we don't
really talk about. Like when I was listening
in to when,
uh,
The Xavier. Xavier. Oh,
sorry. I was like, you too.
Sorry, yeah. Xavier was explaining the Bayesian
optimization to Seth, and I was listening in,
and I could tell that Xavier really understood,
that he wasn't just using, yeah, to do the learning
that he really understood, and that he could
give a presentation on Bayesian optimization.
If we were able to have that confidence in everything,
and every presentation we gave, that would be
really good, even though there are things we
don't know. Like, when Xavier was presenting,
it's like, yeah, there's this.
I didn't really learn a lot about that, but,
like, that's an option and you could go into
that, but this is more central to what we're
talking about.
And so that's not really specific, but...
I think maybe on the manuscript side, it could
be that you are,
we have these kind of staged gates of,
okay,
yes, here's the first draft,
go in and have your learning iteration.
Like,
I'm not here to make revisions on the draft,
I'm here to understand what's here, to then be
able to be able to be able to be able to be.
make better revisions to the second step.
Okay, we should go ahead.
Jump back.